#### **Thomas Andersen**

# Frontend Web-Developer

+45 50927061

mhttps://bk-andersen.com

"In all situations Mr Andersen acted in an extraordinarily responsible, result oriented and conscientious manner. Even for the most difficult challenges, he found very effective solutions, which Mr Andersen always implemented successfully, achieving very good results. The quantity of work he completed and pace at which he worked fulfilled expectations." – Zalando SE

#### Skills

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | ReactJS | Frontend | REST API (Basic understanding) | GitHub |
Customer Support | Music Production | Audio Engineering | English (C2) Danish (C2) German (B2)

Experience

### **Customer Care Specialist**

**Zalando** Berlin, Germany - 01/04/2022 - 31/03/2024

- Specialist in the Customer Care International department of Europe's leading online platform for fashion – Zalando. Being the forefront of a 6 billion EUR company dealing with customer inquiries via email, telephone and chat.
- Processing escalation cases with high priority and handling fraud prevention measures.
- Handling connected retail cases and working as support for stakeholders in B2B support.
- Utilizing both Salesforce as well as CR Tools to handle inquiries from the partners.

## **Music Producer/ Audio Engineer**

Self-employed

Berlin, Germany - 01/07/2018 - Current

- Worked with multiple artists, producing, mixing and mastering music while planning / managing the releases.
- Produced more than 130 instrumental beats for artists to buy or lease through own website.
- Sold more than 200 instrumental beats for artists worldwide.
- Recoded, mixed & mastered close to 100 guitar loops for other beat makers and producers.
- Creating and testing clear and compelling copywriting for digital ads, landing pages and automated email-campaigns.

Education

### **Full-stack Web Development**

Altcademy (Bootcamp)

Remote - 01/01/2024 - Current

Full-stack Web Development with Data Science & Applied AI

### **Bachelor of Arts (Hons)**

**BIMM University** *Berlin, Germany -* 01/10/2015-01/07/2015

Major in Songwriting (Graduating with a First Class Honours Degree).